PORTFOLIO

iunh4533.aithub.io

SKILLS

Coding

HTML CSS Sass

Bootstrap JavaScript

Python Django React.js

SQL Node.js PHP

Software

Visual Studio Code Figma

WordPress Git Github

MYSQL Workbench XAMPP

Dell KACE Trello Slack

LANGUAGES

Fluent Chinese (Cantonese)

Proficient Chinese (Mandarin)

Intermediate Spanish

HOBBIES

Table Tennis Food Touring

Scootering Paintballing

Biking Aspiring wingsuit flyer

CONTACT

P: +1 (347) 295 8842

E: junh4533@gmail.com

A: Brooklyn, NY - USA

SOCIAL

in linkedin.com/in/jun-huang1

github.com/junh4533

JUN HUANG

ABOUT

I am a NYC-based full-stack developer with 2 years of project-based experience in UI/UX prototyping, web app development (with WAMP, MERN, and Python-Django), and custom WordPress theme development. I enjoy working in startup environments where I can collaborate in small teams to create intuitive and practical business solutions.

EDUCATION

MACAULAY HONORS AT CUNY BARUCH COLLEGE - BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

- Major: Computer Information Systems I Minor: NYC Studies with honors
- August 2017 May 2021 I GPA 3.8/4.0

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

fireflies - New York, NY | September 2020 - Present

- Develop reusable components for the client end of our donation platform: fireflies.app/.
- Implement user stories in a SCRUM environment. Coordinate with the CEO/lead UI designer to ensure consistent designs.
- Unit test new pull requests. Also run smoke tests on different scenarios to eliminate UI and functional bugs.

LEAD FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SavingTakeouts - New York, NY | May 2020 - September 2020

- Co-founded a non-profit to provide free web development and marketing services to underprivileged businesses during the COVID-19 pandemic: <u>savingtakeouts.org/</u>.
- Trained and managed team of 4 developers to develop free WordPress themes. Used WP filters and Ajax calls to further customize themes.
- Coordinated daily scrums to set deadlines, update the sprint backlog, and address blockers.
- Operated as a liaison between clients and developers. Translated clients needs into technical specifications for the developers and proposed Figma mockups to our clients.
- Optimized the development process by developing a reusable barebone template with LocalWP. Also integrated Sass modules to ensure modular and locally scoped styles).

WEB DEVELOPER

Baruch College - New York, NY | April 2018 - March 2020

- Collaborated with 4 developers to create web apps that automated file transfers, asset reporting, ticket reporting, and tech support queueing.
- Redesigned the client, staff, and admin interface for Baruch tech support's queue management system that serves 250+ users weekly (using HTML, Sass, Bootstrap, and React.js).
- Developed a CRUD video streaming software using Python-Django that manages and streams promotional videos across multiple Baruch TVs.
- Utilized the WAMP stack to develop a web app that generated and dispatched desktop backgrounds to 700+ Baruch library computers.

LEADERSHIP & ACTIVITIES

PROJECT MANAGER

Ascend - Baruch Chapter I June 2020 - August 2020

- Recruited a team of 10 Ascend memebers to revamp Ascend's 2020 website: ascendbaruch.org.
- Trained team members on Figma prototyping, HTML/CSS development, and WordPress development through weekly workshops. Launched a mobile repsonsive website in under 2 months.

VP OF TECHNOLOGY

Ascend - Baruch Chapter I June 2019 - June 2020

- Spearheaded an 8-week web development (HTML/CSS) workshop and a 10-week Python workshop to introduce students to the world of programming.
- Planned weekly networking sessions, professional panels, and social events.
- Streamlined the e-board's workflow and communication through integrating software like Trello, Slack, and G-Suite.

ACHIVEMENTS

- Member of Phi Eta Sigma National Honors Society | March 2018 Present
- University Scholar (4-year tuition to Macaulay Honors College) | September 2017 Present
- New York City Council Merit Scholarship | September 2017 Present
- Santander Universities Entrepreneurship Scholarship | August 2020
- 5th Annual CUNY Hackathon (Team reFashion) Top 10 | October 2019